123movies.cafe 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy - 123Movies

This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of certain information, including your personal information, by 123Movies.

You control how your personal information is collected, used and disclosed. Other than is necessary to provide you with the service you expect from 123Movies (as explained in this document and when you use our service), 123Movies gives you control over your personal information. 123Movies does not and will not sell or distribute your personal information without your consent.

For instructions on how to contact us, please see the “Contacting Us” section below. By using, visiting or browsing the 123Movies service, you accept and agree to our information practices described below.

_**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**_

We collect information regarding you and your interactions with us and our advertising, your use of our service, applications, sites, tools, and customer service, as well as information regarding your computer or other device used to access our service (such as gaming systems, smart TVs, mobile devices, and set top boxes). This information may include

We may supplement the information described above with information we obtain from other sources, including from both online and offline data providers. Such supplemental information may include demographic data and Internet browsing behavior. We may use this supplemented information for purposes that are consistent with this Privacy Policy, such as: analyzing and understanding our current, former and potential members; improving our service (including our UI experiences), delivery optimization, content selection, recommendation algorithms, advertising and marketing; as well as protecting us and our members from fraud and unauthorized access.

_**USE OF INFORMATION**_

We use the information we collect to provide, analyze, administer, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts for you and others, including to process your registration, your orders and your payments, and to communicate with you on these and other topics. We comply with Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL) and provide users with the ability to opt-in or out of promotional email campaigns and push notifications. For example, we may use the information we collect for purposes such as:

We may use information on an aggregated or anonymous basis. For example, we use movie and TV show ratings and consumption behavior, as well as commentary and reviews, on an aggregate or anonymous basis, to improve our recommendations to you as well as other users. Aggregated or anonymous information may be used for a variety purposes not explicitly set forth in this policy.

_**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**_

Service Providers: We use other companies, agents or contractors (“Service Providers”) to perform services on our behalf or to assist us with the provision of services to you. For example, we engage Service Providers to provide marketing, advertising, communications, infrastructure and IT services, to personalize and optimize our service, to process and limit fraud in connection with credit card transactions or other payment methods, to provide customer service, to collect debts, to analyze and enhance data (including data about users’ interactions with our service), and to process and administer consumer surveys. In the course of providing such services, these Service Providers may have access to your personal or other information. We do not authorize them to use or disclose your personal information except in connection with providing their services.
